Guide to the National Coalition for Haitian Rights Records, 1964-2020, bulk 1982-2004 RL.11314
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files, 1964-2008, undated; bulk 1980-2006; 5; 89 boxes
  - NCHR to Romano L. Mazzoli, 1994 (Box 123)
  - NCHR to Sabalat, 1990 (Box 123)
  - NCHR travel record, 1998 (Box 123)
  - NCHR tribute to Bayard Rustin, undated (Box 148)
  - NCHR trip to Jamaica, 1994 (Box 123)
  - NCHR v. Coast Guard, 1994 (Box 149)
  - NCHR videotapes in conference rooms, undated (Box 123)
  - NCHR, letter from Rosa Herminia Feliz, 1989 (Box 146)
  - NCHR/AW letter of protest, 1992 (Box 123)
  - NCHR-Penitencier National, 1991 (Box 123)
  - NCLR action alert, 1992 (Box 151)
  - NCLR memo, 1989 (Box 123)
  - NECLC 40th anniversary Correspondence/letter, 1991 (Box 123)
  - New Immigration Law, 1986 (Box 123)
  - New York Association for New Americans fax, 1994 (Box 123)
  - New York Campaign to Save ADAP, 1996 (Box 123)
  - New York City Mayor's Office politics towards immigrants, 1997 (Box 123)
  - New York Coalition to Expand Voting, 2006 (Box 123)
  - New York Delegation, 1998 (Box 123)
  - New York Immigration Coalition, 1993 (Box 151)
  - New York Immigration Coalition against Immigration Act of 1996, 1 of 2 (Box 123)
  - New York Immigration Coalition against Immigration Act of 1996, 2 of 2 (Box 124)
  - New York State Democratic Committee, 1994 (Box 124)
  - New York Times news update, 2002 (Box 124)
  - Newcomers in America, 1996 (Box 124)
  - Newest New Yorkers, 2002 (Box 124)
  - News from CRS, 1991 (Box 124)
  - News on immigration, 1993 (Box 124)
  - NGO Amicus Brief Cuban Bar Association et al v. Warren Christopher, 1994 (Box 124)
  - NGO-Forum, Vienna, 1993 (Box 124)
  - NIF memos to all Forum members, 1994 (Box 124)
  - NIF news release, 1995 (Box 124)
  - NIRCF, 1991 (Box 124)
  - NIRCF Board of Directors meeting folder, 1991 (Box 124)
  - NIRCF Board of Directors meeting folder, 1990 (Box 124)
  - NIRCF Board of Directors meeting folder, 1989 (Box 124)
  - NIRCF BOD meeting, 1991 (Box 124)
  - NIRCF Fax memos from 1992, 1 of 3 (Box 124)
  - NIRCF Fax memos from 1992, 2 of 3 (Box 124)
  - NIRCF Fax memos from 1992, 3 of 3 (Box 125)
  - NIRCF info on FAIR, 1993 (Box 147)
  - NIRCF Information Bulletin, 1987 (Box 125)
  - NIRCF memos on Salvadoran Safe Haven Program, 1990 (Box 125)
  - NIRCF proposed bylaws, 1990 (Box 125)
  - NIRCF Sign-On to Congress Regarding Reauthorization of the Refugee Act of 1980, 1991 (Box 125)
  - NIRCF survey, 1989 (Box 125)
  - NJCRAC Action Alert, 1992 (Box 125)
  - NOAH invitation, undated (Box 125)
  - Nomination of Evans Paul for Carter-Menil Human Rights Prize, 1992 (Box 125)
  - Nomination of Evans Paul for the Robert F. Kennedy human rights award, 1992 (Box 125)
  - Notes, 1995 (Box 125)
  - Nov. 29 inquiry controversy, 1989 (Box 125)
  - NY Bar Association Immigration Law update, 1987 (Box 148)
  - NY Board of Education election, 1996 (Box 125)
  - NY Department of Education, 2005 (Box 126)
  - NY Human Resources Administration memo, 1993 (Box 126)
  - NY State Legislation Process, 1991 (Box 126)
  - NYIC announcements, 1997 (Box 126)
  - NYIC Citizenship, 1998 (Box 126)
  - NYIC Educations Issues Task Force meeting, 1997 (Box 126)
  - NYIC General Membership meeting, 1994 (Box 126)
  - NYIC general membership meeting minutes, 1991 (Box 126)
  - NYIC- Immigration News, 1998 (Box 126)
  - NYIC immigration news, 1998 (Box 126)
  - NYIC School Board Elections, 1998 (Box 126)
  - NYIC Speakers Bureau, 1997 (Box 126)
  - NYIC to McCalla, 1991 (Box 126)
  - NYIC training on welfare reform and immigrants, 1996 (Box 126)
  - NYIC- Welfare, 1996-1998 (Box 126)
  - NYPD, updated, undated (Box 126)
  - NYT articles on Haitian refugees, 1994 (Box 126)
  - NYU project, 1996 (Box 126)
  - OAS - Press Release on Bazin, 1992 (Box 126)
  - OAS- "Restoration of Democracy in Haiti", 1991 (Box 126)
  - OAS accord, 1992 (Box 132)
  - OAS Ad-Hoc Meeting of Ministers of Foreign Affairs, 1991 (Box 126)
  - OAS- InterAmerican Commission on Human Rights Reponses to CHRCL Petition Challenging, 1993 (Box 126)
  - OAS meeting documents, 1989 (Box 127)
  - OAS- Ministers of Foreign Affairs, 1991 (Box 127)
  - OAS petition for Jean-Auguste Mesyeux, Evans Paul, Sgt. Etienne Marineau, 1990 (Box 127)
  - OAS precautionary measures, 1995 (Box 127)
  - OAS press release, 1990 (Box 127)
  - OAS press release/Statement by OAS Secretary General, 1993-1994 (Box 127)
  - OAS report, 1989 (Box 127)
  - OAS Statement on Democratic Haiti, 1991 (Box 127)
  - OAS Support Haitian Government, 1991 (Box 127)
  - OAS/UN Communique, 1993 (Box 127)
  - Observer mission to Kingston (Jamaica), 1994 (Box 127)
  - ODEMOBA program documents, 1995 (Box 127)
  - OGITH (Organization Generale Independente des Travailleurs Haitiens) Brochure, 1989 (Box 127)
  - Oman Desanges, 1994 (Box 146)
    [contains graphic material]
  - ONE-respe education and community work, undated (Box 127)
  - ONM investigation report, 1996 (Box 151)
  - Op-ed on Pascal Trouillot government, 1990 (Box 127)
  - Op-Ed on proposed US Military aid to the Haitian army, 1990 (Box 127)
  - Open Society Institute Forced Migration Projects, 1995 (Box 127)
  - Open Society Institute Materials, 1994 (Box 127)
  - Open Statement on the Human Rights Situation in Haiti, 2000 (Box 127)
  - Operation Kenbe, 1992 (Box 127)
  - OR- O'Daniel P. Bastiani case, 1988 (Box 127)
  - Oraison of Izmery, 1992 (Box 127)
  - Organization Statements on Executive Order, 1992 (Box 127)
  - Original Materials for "Hoy the Story", 1992; 1 of 3 (Box 127)
  - Original Materials for "Hoy the Story", 1992; 2 of 3 (Box 127)
  - Original Materials for "Hoy the Story", 1992; 3 of 3 (Box 127)
  - Oversight Hearing on Cuban and Haitian Immigration, 1991 (Box 128)
  - Overview of Haiti, 1988 (Box 128)
  - Overview of human rights, 1989 (Box 128)
  - Overview of human rights conditions in Haiti, undated (Box 128)
  - Overview of major political events in Haiti, 1981-1994 (Box 128)
  - Oxfam America update, 1992 (Box 128)
  - Oxfam: Haiti Communications Project, 1991 (Box 128)
  - PANPRA (Pati Nasyonalis Pwogresis Revolisyone Ayisyen), 1990 (Box 128)
  - PANPRA statement, 1990 (Box 128)
  - Paraison Info, 1990-1991 (Box 128)
  - PARINAC Global Conference, 1994 (Box 128)
  - PARINAC NGO Consultation panel "The Right to Seek Asylum", 1994 (Box 128)
  - Parliamentarians call for safety of Haitian legislators, 1992 (Box 128)
  - Parti Nationaliste Progressiste Revolutionnaire Haitien, 1990 (Box 146)
  - Parti Unifie Des Communistes Haitiens, 1989 (Box 128)
  - Partial list of Candidates for the CEP, 1995 (Box 128)
  - Participants at meeting on New Immigration Legislation, 1986 (Box 148)
  - Participants in the reunion in San Pedro, 1990 (Box 128)
  - Participants of July 14, 1995 (Box 128)
  - Pastoral Care of Migrants and Refugees News, 1986 (Box 128)
  - Pastoral Haitiana, 1997 (Box 128)
  - Pastoral Haitiana from F. Paraison, 1991 (Box 128)
  - Patricia Parker to George Shultz, 1986 (Box 128)
  - Patrick Gavigan, Confidential Correspondence/letter with International Organization for Migration, 1996 (Box 128)
  - Paul Jean Mario, 1992 (Box 128)
  - Pax Christi, 1993 (Box 128)
  - Pax Christi update, 1991 (Box 128)
  - Pax Christi: Haiti Action Alert, 1991 (Box 128)
  - Peace and Justice Commission reports, 1993 (Box 128)
  - Peace and Justice Commission reports, 1990-1992 (Box 128)
  - Peacekeeping in Haiti- IPA forum, 1996 (Box 129)
  - Pedro Ruquoy i.e.: passage to US of three guests, 1992 (Box 129)
  - PEN American Center Protest, 1993 (Box 129)
  - PEN/Barbara Goldsmith Award, 1992 (Box 129)
  - Penal Reform, 1987-1996; 1 of 2 (Box 129)
  - Penal Reform, 1987-1996; 2 of 2 (Box 129)
  - People arrested illegally, 1991 (Box 129)
  - Perodin events and killings, 1990 (Box 146)
  - Perodin events and killings [h], 1990 (Box 129)
  - Perspectives Haiti Bulletin, 1992 (Box 129)
  - Peter A. Schey to NCHR, 1990 (Box 129)
  - Peter A. Schey, CHRCL to McCalla, NCHR, 1994 (Box 129)
  - Petition to Senator Spencer Abraham, 1998 (Box 129)
  - Petitions to support HR 3663, 1994 (Box 129)
  - Phil Donahue Show Haitian Refugees, 1993 (Box 129)
  - Physicians for Human Rights, 1990 (Box 129)
  - Physicians for Human Rights, 1990 (Box 129)
  - Physicians for Human Rights Correspondence/letters, 1990 (Box 129)
  - Physicians for Human Rights Materials, 1993 (Box 129)
  - Physicians for Human Rights memo, 1989 (Box 129)
  - Physicians for Human Rights notes from Haiti, 1990 (Box 129)
  - Piatre Massacre reports, 1990 (Box 129)
  - Pierre Esperance - letters of support, 1999; 1 of 3 (Box 115)
  - Pierre Esperance - letters of support, 1999; 2 of 3 (Box 115)
  - Pierre Esperance - letters of support, 1999; 3 of 3 (Box 115)
  - Pierre Louis Leibnitz, undated (Box 129)
  - Plateforme, 1991 (Box 129)
  - Platform Human Rights Conference, 1992 (Box 129)
  - POHDH Fax, list of enemies, 1999 (Box 129)
  - Police - "Law Project About the Creation of the National Police of Haiti", 1993 (Box 130)
  - Police - "The Reforms of Haitian Police", 1998 (Box 130)
  - Police - bill draft on creation of a national police [h], 1993 (Box 130)
  - Police - Correspondence/letter campaign Carrefour Feuilles police killings, 1999 (Box 130)
  - Police - Correspondence/letter to request investigation on alleged human rights violation by the police, 1999 (Box 130)
  - Police - Haiti Police Reform, 1995-1997; 2 of 2 (Box 130)
  - Police - Haiti Police Reform Reports, 2005 (Box 130)
  - Police - Human Rights Record of the Haitian Police, 1997 (Box 152)
  - Police - International Community and Police Reform in Central America and Haiti, 1994 (Box 130)
  - Police - Meetings regarding police training in Haiti [h], 1997 (Box 130)
  - Police - notes on police shooting of 4 youths, 1991 (Box 130)
  - Police - Police and immigration, 1992 (Box 130)
  - Police - Police brutality (LEAP), 1999-2000 (Box 130)
  - Police - Police brutality, Ella Baker Center, and Center for Constitutional Rights, 1997-1998 (Box 131)
  - Police - Police Department, 1999 (Box 131)
  - Police - police interview, 1991 (Box 131)
  - Police - Police issues, 1996 (Box 131)
  - Police - Police profiling article, 1999 (Box 131)
  - Police - police reform, 1992 (Box 131)
  - Police - proposed law on civilian national police, 1991 (Box 131)
  - Police - Religious Coalition Against Police Brutality, 2000 (Box 131)
  - Police - Reports and intelligence regarding Mirebalais events (police killings), 1998 (Box 131)
  - Police - Truth Commission Police Force, 1994 (Box 131)
  - Police - WOLA: Police Reform Conference, 1994 (Box 131)
  - Political Causes of Emigration, 1979 (Box 131)
  - Political options re: ecology in Haiti article, 1996 (Box 131)
  - Political parties in Haiti [h], 1995 (Box 131)
  - Post-election statement, 1990 (Box 131)
  - PR for de facto regime, 1992 (Box 131)
  - Precautionary Measures Taken by the Inter-American Commission in Case No. 10.675 at 83rd period session, 1993 (Box 131)
  - Preliminary report from delegation trip to Haiti, 1992 (Box 132)
  - Prepared statement of William G. O'Neill, 1991 (Box 132)
  - Preparing for Legalization Interviews, undated (Box 132)
  - Presbyterian Disaster Assistance, 1998 (Box 132)
  - Presbyterian UN office, 1996 (Box 132)
  - Pre-Screening at US Airports, 1992 (Box 132)
  - President Bush, 1990 (Box 132)
  - President Bush executive order prohibiting transactions to Haiti, 1991 (Box 132)
  - President Clinton letter- draft, 1992 (Box 132)
  - President Clinton press release, 1994 (Box 132)
  - President Clinton to Jonathan Demme, 1995 (Box 132)
  - President Clinton's Radio Address to the Haitian people, 1993 (Box 132)
  - Presidential election tallies, 1990 (Box 132)
  - Presidential Proclamation 5928 of 12/27/88, 1988 (Box 132)
  - Press advisory, 1991 (Box 132)
  - Press conference, 1992 (Box 132)
  - Presumption and Stability and Moot Asylum, undated (Box 132)
  - Prime Minister Jacques Edouard Alexis, 1999 (Box 149)
  - Prime Ministry Cabinet to McCalla from Prime Ministry Cabinet, 1993 (Box 132)
  - Prison project, 1986 (Box 132)
  - Prison Report PHR, 1990-1991 (Box 132)
  - Prison report by Victor Cuffy, 1991 (Box 132)
  - Prisoner correspondence Honorat Kashkett, 1990 (Box 132)
  - Prisoner list, 1989 (Box 132)
  - Prisoners from Kil de Sak, 1965-1970 (Box 116)
  - Privatization in Haiti article, 1996 (Box 133)
  - Problems facing Haiti's unwanted refugees at home, 1990 (Box 133)
  - Pro-Bono Training Program to Assist Haitian Refugees, 1992; 1 of 2 (Box 133)
  - Pro-Bono Training Program to Assist Haitian Refugees, 1992; 2 of 2 (Box 133)
  - Proclamation from the State Council, 1990 (Box 133)
  - Profile of asylum claims - Haiti, 1995 (Box 133)
  - Profile of Haitian organizations, 1986 (Box 133)
  - Program in International Policy Attitudes News Release, 1994 (Box 133)
  - Project for the framing of Domestic Children, 1987 (Box 133)
  - Project statutes, undated (Box 133)
  - Projecto Libertad, 1989-1990 (Box 133)
  - Proposal for Haiti Government violation commission, 1991 (Box 133)
  - Proposal Haiti Projects, 1992 (Box 133)
  - Proposed criminal alien legislation, 1990 (Box 133)
  - Proposed Immigration Sub-Committee Substitute Amendment to S. 1333, 1994 (Box 133)
  - Proposed migration law and supporting materials, 1991 (Box 133)
  - Proposed resolution on Human Rights in Haiti, 1993 (Box 133)
  - Protest Campaign Against the movie "How Stella Got Her Groove Back", 1998 (Box 133)
  - protest letters over jailed deportees, 1990 (Box 147)
  - Protest NCHR Americas Watch, 1990 (Box 133)
  - Protest of Haitian neglect under Clinton, 1994 (Box 133)
  - Protest rally against FDA's discrimination towards Haitians, 1990 (Box 133)
  - Protest/fast for Haitian repatriation decision, 1994 (Box 133)
  - Protests- others respond to jailed deportees, 1990 (Box 133)
  - Provisional Electoral Council, Haiti Electoral Law, 1995 (Box 133)
  - Public Advocate for NY to Howard Safir, 1997 (Box 133)
  - Puebla Institute- election report, 1990 (Box 133)
  - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1987 (Box 133)
  - Pwogram Gouvènman, Rene Theodore, undated (Box 133)
  - Quarantined by the USA, 1992 (Box 133)
  - Questionnaire for people arrested arbitrarily, 1992 (Box 133)
  - Questionnaire for Refugees, undated (Box 133)
  - Questionnaire: How to Interrogate Witness to Specific HR Abuse, 1991 (Box 134)
  - Quixote Center, 1993 (Box 134)
  - Quixote Center to Friends of Haiti, 1992 (Box 134)
  - Radio Enriquillo, 1992 (Box 134)
  - Radio Enriquillo, 1992 (Box 134)
  - Radio Soleil letter to McCalla, 1989 (Box 134)
  - Radyo Soley, 1988-1989 (Box 134)
  - Rainbow lobby campaign and conference, 1990 (Box 146)
  - Ramon Portomal notes, undated (Box 134)
  - Rankont TKL nasyonal, 1991 (Box 134)
  - Raoul Cedras, 1992 (Box 134)
  - Raoul Peck Event, 1996 (Box 134)
  - Rayna Rapp to Rev. Bevilacqua about Hooper Fund, 1988 (Box 134)
  - Raynard Pierre and Lafontant correspondence, 1987 (Box 134)
  - RDC press release, 1989 (Box 134)
  - Recent developments in Haiti, 1993 (Box 146)
  - Reception to Nova human rights defendant Chihana and Evans Paul, 1992 (Box 134)
  - Recovery of Duvalier Family Assets, 1986 (Box 134)
  - Recovery of Duvalier Family Assets [h.], 1986 (Box 134)
  - Red Cross Info, 1989 (Box 134)
  - Reestablishment of Democracy in Haiti, 1992 (Box 134)
  - Reflections on the external cooperation, undated (Box 134)
  - Reform of the Justice System and Assistance to the Parliament [h], undated (Box 134)
  - Refugee Advocacy Program, 1996 (Box 134)
  - Refugee aid correspondence, 1994 (Box 134)
  - Refugee and Immigration Issues in the 1990s conference folder (Box 134)
  - Refugee and Migration Affairs, 1994 (Box 134)
  - Refugee and migration affairs, 1994 (Box 134)
  - Refugee Assistance Council to Mr. Hickle, 1993 (Box 134)
  - Refugee Data, 1994 (Box 134)
  - Refugee files, 1995 (Box 134)
  - Refugee jainero, 1998 (Box 134)
  - Refugee Processing, 1994 (Box 134)
  - Refugee Processing in Haiti, 1993 (Box 134)
  - Refugee release letter to McCalla, 1990 (Box 135)
  - Refugee resettlement Ch. 1, 1996 (Box 135)
  - Refugee statements, 1991 (Box 135)
  - Refugee Statistics, 1981-1994 (Box 135)
  - Refugee Supply Co., 1994 (Box 135)
  - Refugee voices and DOS i.e.: Haitian repatriation, 1992 (Box 135)
  - Refugees, 1990 (Box 151)
  - Refugees and Immigration, 2000 (Box 135)
  - Refugees Interdicted since the May 8 change of policy, 1994 (Box 135)
  - Refugees jailed, 1990 (Box 147)
  - Refugees- press release, 1989 (Box 135)
  - Regine McCalla speech "Haitian Women and Children Refugees", 1990 (Box 148)
  - Release plea, undated (Box 135)
  - Release presentation and reporting, 1986 (Box 135)
  - Release representation and reporting- Spellman cases, 1986 (Box 135)
  - Religious Leaders Arrested in Haiti, 1992 (Box 135)
  - Remarks by Mayor Dinkins, 1991 (Box 135)
  - Remarks of Ambassador Luigi R. Einaudi, 1992 (Box 135)
  - Remarks on draft petition, 1990 (Box 135)
  - RENADWAM (Rezo Nasyonal Pou Defann Dwa Moun), 1988 (Box 135)
  - RENADWAM notice on violation of Haitian Constitution, 1987 (Box 135)
  - Rene Preval correspondence, 1991 (Box 135)
  - Rene Preval correspondence, 1991 (Box 135)
  - Rene Preval letter, 1991 (Box 135)
  - Rene Proval, disappearance of illegal prisoner, 1991 (Box 135)
  - Re-opening of schools, 1995-1996 (Box 135)
  - Repatriation notes, 1995-1996 (Box 125)
  - Repatriation notes, undated (Box 125)
  - Repatriation of Haitian refugees, c. 1992 (Box 135)
  - Repatriation report, 1992 (Box 147)
  - Repatriations actions, 1992 (Box 152)
  - Replenishment Agricultural Workers (RAW) program, 1989 (Box 135)
  - Report- "Formation Program", 1996 (Box 135)
  - Report- "The Case of Dr. Roger Lafontant", undated (Box 135)
  - Report and Prayer of an arrested youth, 1992 (Box 150)
  - Report by Arhault Jean-Phillipe, Juriste, 1992-1993 (Box 135)
  - Report from Beatrice re: refugees, 1991 (Box 135)
  - Report from Ulrick Monpremier, 1991 (Box 135)
  - Report in Kreyol, 1989 (Box 135)
  - Report of an NCC Delegation to Haiti, 1992 (Box 135)
  - Report of mission to Haiti, 1994 (Box 135)
  - Report of UNCHR Ex Com Session, 1994 (Box 135)
  - Report on 1996 training program (Box 135)
  - Report on agriculture and poverty, 1989 (Box 135)
  - Report on commission, undated (Box 136)
  - Report on Haitian American Cultural and Social Organization, undated (Box 136)
  - Report on NCHR first Human Rights Training Seminar, 1995 (Box 136)
  - Report on Père Renaud François, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Report on political actions in Haiti [h], 1991 (Box 136)
  - Report on the assassination or Antoine Izmery, undated (Box 136)
  - Report to NCHR, 1992 (Box 136)
  - Report to the Puerto Rican Institute for Civil Rights, undated (Box 136)
  - Report to Tom Wensky on Haiti, 1991 (Box 136)
  - Reporters Sons Frontiers to Raoul Cedras, 1994 (Box 136)
  - Reports by Congressman Donald Payne, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Reports from Haiti Delegation, 1992 (Box 136)
  - Reports of human rights violations, Northeast Haiti, 1991-1994 (Box 136)
  - Reports on protest against repatriation, 1992 (Box 136)
  - Reports on Refugees, 1994 (Box 136)
  - reports on rejected Haitian asylum- seekers, 1994 (Box 136)
  - Representation of different sections of Haitian society, 1991 (Box 136)
  - Repression against teachers in Haiti, 1992 (Box 136)
  - Repression and abuse ("bone-crushing") in Grand Goave from 1991-1992, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Repression and abuse in Grand Goave, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Repression in Grand Goâve files, 1991-1992 (Box 136)
  - Request to open a special account within Haiti Central Bank [h.], 1986 (Box 136)
  - Research on regional migrations, 1995 (Box 136)
  - Resident Illegal Alien population estimate, 1992 (Box 151)
  - Resident Status irregularity Individual Case, 1990 (Box 136)
  - Resolution 220: A Bill to Assist Haitian Refugees, 1991 (Box 136)
  - Resolution by Senator Graham, 1988 (Box 136)
  - Resource list for newly arrived Haitian in NYC, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Respectful and effective policing, 1999 (Box 136)
  - Restavek Haiti, 2000 (Box 136)
  - Return of Roger Lafontant, 1990 (Box 136)
  - Return to despotism - press release, 1990 (Box 132)
  - Rick Swartz, 1992 (Box 117)
  - Rights and Wrongs TV Program, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Robert Duval from NCHR, 1987 (Box 149)
  - Robert E. Kennedy Human Rights Award, 1992 (Box 136)
  - Robert F. Kennedy Memorial Center for Human Rights, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Robert Olhaye Correspondence, 1994 (Box 136)
  - Robert Rubiri's Winner of Mickey Lelant's Award- Refugee Voices, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Roberta G. Lentz, 1990 (Box 148)
  - Roberto Cuellar, 1991 (Box 136)
  - Roberto Cuellar, course on Human Rights, 1991 (Box 136)
  - Roger Lafontant, 1984 (Box 136)
  - Roger LaFontante FOIA, 1992-1998 (Box 136)
  - Ronald Michael Segal, South Africa, 1990 (Box 136)
  - Rural Florida tour notes, 1983 (Box 125)
  - Safe Haven Program for Haitian Asylum Seekers, 1989-1996 (Box 137)
  - Salarz Proposed Legislation, 1992 (Box 137)
  - Salvadorans Safe Haven update, 1993 (Box 137)
  - Sant Kal Levèk, 1987 (Box 137)
  - Sant Kal Levèk proposal, 1987 (Box 137)
  - Sant Kal Levèk to McCalla, 1989 (Box 137)
  - Sant Pwomosyon Moun, 1989 (Box 137)
  - Sant Pwomosyon Moun Correspondence, 1990 (Box 137)
  - Sant Pwomosyon Moun: Resolutions du Colloque, 1990 (Box 137)
  - Save Program- articles, statements, 1986 (Box 137)
  - Schiller Marcelin speech, 1992 (Box 137)
  - Schomburg Center for Black Culture, 1993 (Box 137)
  - Schumer- Agricultural proposal, 1986 (Box 137)
  - Screening of "The Man by the Shore" of Raoul Peck, 1995 (Box 137)
  - Secretary of state Christopher, request for temporary protected status, 1994 (Box 137)
  - Secretary of State James Baker, undated (Box 137)
  - Secretary of State Warren Christopher, 1993 (Box 137)
  - Section chiefs Reinstated after coup, 1992 (Box 137)
  - Security Precautions on trips, 1992 (Box 137)
  - SELA: Understanding Jean Rabel, 1987 (Box 137)
  - Selor Josaphat plea for help, 1992-1993 (Box 137)
  - Seminar on refugee assistance, 1994 (Box 137)
  - Sen. Daniel Moynihan from McCalla, 1991 (Box 151)
  - Sen. Edward Kennedy Statement, 1992 (Box 137)
  - Senate target list on Haiti issues, 1992 (Box 147)
  - Senators/Representatives phone and room directory, undated (Box 137)
  - September Events in Haiti, 1988 (Box 137)
  - Serge Beaulieu correspondence, 1991 (Box 137)
  - Sisters of the Humility of Mary, 2003 (Box 137)
  - Small Old Catholic Church, 2000 (Box 137)
  - Soares, 1992 (Box 137)
  - Social and judicial roots of violence against women [h], 1993 (Box 137)
  - SOFA (Kreyol), 1991 (Box 137)
  - Solar power in Haiti, 1992 (Box 137)
  - Some traits of Jean-Jacques Honorat, 1991 (Box 137)
  - Songwriters' Association of Washington, 1992 (Box 137)
  - Soros Foundation in Haiti, 1995 (Box 138)
  - Soviet Aid Bill, 1992 (Box 116)
  - SPJ- Resolution Evans Paul, 1991 (Box 138)
  - Sponsors Organized to Assist Refugees (SOAD) update faxes, 1993 (Box 138)
  - St. Vincent and the Grenadines Human Rights Association, 1990-1991 (Box 138)
  - State Department briefing, 1991 (Box 138)
  - State Department briefings on Haiti, 1993 (Box 138)
  - State Department chain of command for Haiti emergencies, 1991 (Box 138)
  - State Department press briefing, undated (Box 138)
  - State Department Press Release on Diplomatic Initiative, 1993 (Box 138)
  - State Department Statistics on Refugees and Resettlement, 1992 (Box 138)
  - State Department telegrams, 1992 (Box 138)
  - State of Diege- Legal Complaint, 1990 (Box 138)
  - State of siege notes, undated (Box 138)
  - Statement and Press Conference by the President, 1994 (Box 138)
  - Statement before the Inter-American Commission on Human Rights Situation in Haiti, J.McCalla, 2000 (Box 138)